[lively drum tapping]
[mysterious music playing]
["Let's Swim" by Stela Campos
& Érico Theobaldo playing]
-[water splashes]
-[people chatter]
♪ You might think that I'm the stranger ♪
♪ You might think but you don't know me ♪
[boy narrator] I never understood why in
The Little Mermaid Ariel traded the ocean
for a boring prince.
I love being in the water.
♪Might think but you don't know me ♪
♪ You might think that you can't hurt me ♪
♪ Just look at me ♪
[boy narrator] At least, I used to.
♪ Oh oh oh
I'll never let you down ♪
♪ Oh oh oh ♪
-[bell rings]
-♪ I will know you swim like a dolphin ♪
[boy narrator] I am fat.
I'm not cute and chubby, I am huge.
I take up space.
-Everyone an earthquake!
-[people shouting]
Make way! Make way!
The earthquake's coming!
[boy narrator] A whole month away
from this school.
Jeez, it's gonna be tough.
I don't know how I'll make it.
♪ I'll never let you down ♪
[boy narrator] Here are a few of
the reasons I'll miss this school so much.
♪ Oh oh
You never let me down ♪
[boy narrator] Reason number one.
It's such an inclusive environment.
LARDASS
TODAY IS THE DAY
[students chatter and laugh]
Did you hear Marcelo kissed
Felipe at the front gate?
Was it Hot Felipe or Fat Felipe?
[boy narrator] Reason number two.
I just feel so loved and appreciated here.
[whistle blows]
All right, let's go. Fatso, come on.
You like playing with balls, right?
[boy 1 chuckles]
[boy 2] This is gonna suck.
[boy narrator] Reason number three.
It's the best place
to deal with my anxiety.
-[boy 3] Goal!
-[students shout]
♪ Oh oh
Through these emotions ♪
[boy narrator] You see, in this wonderful,
idyllic, flawless paradise,
being fat really isn't a problem.
BASED ON THE NOVEL BY VITOR MARTINS
A whole vacation away from this place.
Ah, I can finally be alone
without anyone bothering me.
And the best part is, I don't have
to set foot outside the house.
[exhales deeply]
HERE THE WHOLE TIME
I can do whatever I want.
Play video games, read manga,
take afternoon naps
and appreciate the best
that streaming has to offer.
"Your Heart is My Destiny."
-Looks like a terrible movie. I love it.
-[electronic bleep]
[emotional music playing]
My love,
I've replayed this moment
a thousand times in my mind,
and it never feels right.
Walking away feels like
losing something I'll never find again.
If any part of you still wonders
what we could've been,
you know where to find me.
[whimsical music playing]
[woman chatters over speaker]
Thank you.
[woman continues chattering]
Wait! Wait!
Don't get on this bus!
[boy narrator] I wish life
was like a romantic comedy.
Just take off your glasses
and automatically become beautiful.
I have one last thing… to say to you.
[kissing]
[music becomes emotional]
[boy narrator] But in real life,
a hot guy like that would never want me.
[horn honks]
-[music continues]
-[knocking]
[woman] Felipe? Hey.
The weather's so nice.
You sure you don't wanna go to the pool?
-No, Mom, I'm watching a movie right now.
-Why won't you go? Hm?
You know I hate swimming pools.
-"I hate swimming pools."
-Mom! Stop it, Or I'll do it back.
-I will!
-Stop! Come on, you're on vacation.
-If you're gonna stay holed up… Ew!
-[cell phone ringing]
-They'll be here soon. Clean your room.
-Stop, that's embarrassing! Who's coming?
-Wait who?
-Hey, how are you?
Wait, mom. Wait a minute.
Who's on the way?
-[people chatter and scream]
-[moody contemplative music playing]
-[faucet handle squeaks]
-[water running]
♪ The crab is such a sight to see
You're gonna get to ♪
♪ Hanging out with old sardines
In conversation ♪
♪ I've been dancing
At the sand bar for my whole life ♪
♪ And the octopus is still out back
Serve a soda ♪
♪ Dah dah dah ♪
♪ The dolphin is a dancer
He likes to stomp his fins ♪
♪ And the giant squid
Is always going to spin ♪
♪ The clams all clap their shells ♪
♪ The fish flop around as well ♪
♪ The lobsters spin around
and their tails go… ♪ [gasps]
♪ Bar, bar, bar
I wanna go to the sandbar ♪
We're gonna go to the sandbar ♪
♪ We're coming
Bar, bar, bar, we're gonna go to… ♪
-[both scream]
-[lively music playing]
[music fades]
What is this guy doing here?
I told you. Didn't I tell you?
Yeah, Sandra's going on vacation.
Mm, a conference for Mauro.
-You didn't tell me.
-Could've sworn I did.
-You didn't ask me, and you--
-Would you like sugar?
No, I like it black. He would stay
with my sister, but something came up.
Oh, well, 15 days will fly by.
15 days? Mom, 15 days? Are you serious?
-This shit was a bad idea.
-[Sandra] Caio Luiz!
-I'm so sorry.
-No, I'm sorry. I don't know what to say.
I'm the one who's sorry. Come on.
Let's go. Let's step outside.
You and I are gonna have a little talk.
-[Caio] I'm going. I don't wanna stay.
-[Sandra] Stop complaining. Shh!
I don't want anyone to hear.
15 days is almost the whole vacation.
Sweetie, she watered our plants
when we went to the trip to Gramado.
-How can I say no?
-When we got back, they were all dead.
-Right, she overwatered them.
-Yeah.
It'll be good for you. You need to get out
of your room, hang out with people.
-It'll be great.
-I'm staying in my room.
He's 16 years old, he can stay home alone.
Only 16 years old.
Last time I tried
to leave you on your own--
I thought you already punished me.
Now you're trying to ditch me.
You know what? I get it. I also really
don't think it's the best option, I don't.
-Felipe is a little--
-Mom…
What, sweetie?
It's not like he tries to hide it.
But this is the best we could get.
And you two already know each other.
No, Mom, we used to. We haven't spoken
in years. He clearly hates me.
Of course I hate him. You saw how he is.
He won't even respond
to "good morning" in the elevator.
[upbeat music playing]
Good morning.
He's one of those gym guys.
-[grunting]
-[lively whimsical music playing]
He's a straight dude who's into dude
stuff, like there's shooter games,
he only reads fantasy.
Mom, he likes football.
-[shouting]
-[energetic techno music playing]
[all cheering]
[whistle blows]
-Worst kind of straight dude.
-Is there a good kind of straight dude?
Don't start cracking jokes
after stabbing me in the back.
I get it, all right?
I understand you don't want to compromise.
You are staying here!
You're staying here, dammit, that's all!
-You're too old to act like this.
-I'm old now?
-Yes, you are too old!
-The bags are already in the car.
Cutting it close to get to the airport.
We've gotta leave now.
-All right.
-[contemplative music playing]
Is there a problem?
-It's fine.
-It's all good.
-Then let's go.
-All right. Say bye to your dad.
-See you.
-Bye, sweetie.
-Behave yourself. Come on.
-Love you. Behave yourself.
[music stops]
[Felipe's mom] Tidy your room
and get the bed ready for him.
You invited him. Tidy up your own room.
He's not staying in my room.
-Lord help us all.
-[Caio] I'll sleep on the couch.
[gentle guitar music playing]
-Sorry, pal.
-[Felipe] Let me through.
-Let me through, Mom. Thank you. Finally.
-Fine. Go!
[Caio] Hey.
What's the Wi-Fi password?
Merylstreep1979.
She won her first Oscar that year.
Uh… How do you spell Meryl Streep?
DAY 1
[screams and grunts]
[alert on cell phone]
OLIVIA, I REALLY GOTTA TALK TO YOU.
WHEN CAN YOU SEE ME?
[door opens and closes]
SURE, FELIPE. WHAT TIME CAN YOU…
My mom brought a guy into the house.
-Good afternoon, Felipe.
-Good afternoon.
Sorry, I couldn't wait
for our next appointment.
Your mother obviously
has the right to date.
That was something we discussed.
Not like this though, Olivia. It's the
neighbor's son. He's staying for 15 days.
Do you know what it's like to be stuck
for 15 days in your house with a stranger?
Anything worse than that?
After 20 years as a psychologist,
I can assure you yes, there is.
I won't survive this.
If I die, I'm gonna blame you.
You're not gonna die.
And you need to learn
a little more about boundaries.
We'll talk about it
at your next appointment.
No one in the world has it worse than me.
[tense music playing]
[music becomes ominous]
The victim's body looked like a sieve.
-Looks like we're dealing with a monster.
-Exactly.
And that's why I'm gonna be
assigning you a new partner.
[Felipe] A partner?
-I'm sorry, but I work much better alone.
-I know.
He's only gonna end up
slowing me down. It's a terrible idea.
-What're you trying to say?
-Exactly what you think I'm saying.
All right, enough.
You don't have a choice.
From now on, you two--
-[audio distortion]
-[music stops]
-[Caio] That's it. Okay.
-[player] Copy that. I'll follow you.
-[character] Bomb has been planted.
-Nah, you got this. I'll meet you there.
-[character] Go! Go! Go!
-Hold on.
You need something?
Wi-Fi is slow.
Think you could pause that?
[chuckles] No, that's not my dad, no.
Game's live so I can't pause it.
You can wait a minute.
-[video game explosion]
-No, don't be dumb. You can't go alone.
Wait. I'm coming.
-[player] Where you at?
-Calm down! I'm coming. No, don't go in!
-No!
-[player chatters]
[electronic chime]
[intriguing music playing]
Sweet dreams.
["Gives You Hell"
by The Countdown Singers playing]
♪ Now where's your picket fence, love? ♪
DAY 2
[Felipe's mom] And she was
this tiny thing following you around.
-Mom, what are you listening to?
-Isn't it great?
I know, Caio put it on.
Hey. Good morning.
WORLD'S BEST SON
♪ And truth be told, I'm lying ♪
♪ When you see my face
Hope it gives you hell ♪
♪ Hope it gives you hell ♪
♪ When you walk my way
Hope it gives you hell ♪
♪ Hope it gives you hell ♪
♪ If you find a man that's worth a damn
And treats you well ♪
♪ Then he's a fool
You're just as well ♪
♪ Hope it gives you hell ♪
♪ Tomorrow, you'll be thinking
to yourself ♪
♪ "Yeah, where did it all go wrong?" ♪
♪ But the list goes on and on ♪
♪ When you see my face
Hope it gives you hell ♪
-♪ Hope it gives you hell ♪
♪ You can sing along
I hope that it puts you through hell ♪
-Mom. Mom, where's my towel?
-["Gives You Hell" ends]
-Caio asked for one to go to the pool.
-[phone rings]
But Mom, you should have--
-Mom?
-Yeah? Hi, Francisco.
Okay, I'll be right down. Thank you.
You had to give him mine? Wow.
Felipe, it's just a towel.
He asked for one, I gave him one.
-Can you go down and get a package for me?
-[sighs] No, Mom…
I'm all dirty. Go on.
[Francisco] Hi, Felipe.
All right.
Here it is.
Just sign here.
[chatter over speaker]
And this one here's for Caio.
He's out at the pool.
Why can't you take it?
I can't leave my post.
That would be dangerous.
No. Dangerous is going somewhere I detest
and interacting with someone
I don't want to.
Is that person armed though?
No.
Then you see? Much less dangerous.
[intriguing music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
I'm fed up. Two more weeks
stuck with that pain in the ass.
I ordered food down here
just so I wouldn't have to stay up there.
Lunch, Your Majesty.
Thanks.
Gandalf dies at the end.
THE LORD OF THE RINGS PART 1
-Why would you do that?
-Well, 'cause I'm a pain in the ass.
You've been a jerk since yesterday.
I didn't do anything to you.
Not my fault you haven't seen
a movie from 20 years ago.
Fat fucking asshole.
What's wrong with you.
Give me my towel.
Think I wanna stay with you?
I shouldn't be there!
At least we agree on that!
-Let go of the--
-Let go of--
[both scream]
[people scream]
[Sandra] They have to close the pool
in the summer!
Do you have any idea what
that bonehead shit will cost your dad?
-It's not my fault, Mom!
-Yes, it is.
But you're not the one paying, Caio.
I'm sure you know
your dad's really gonna be upset.
Do you have any idea what those oils cost?
None of this would've happened
if you had said no.
Quit it! You're not a kid anymore.
-Are you gonna listen to me or not?
-What was that?
You're not talking
to one of your lesbian friends.
I'm your Mom. Wash your face, it's
disgusting. We're done, I'm hanging up.
[bleep on phone]
You and Caio have to go to the store.
No.
-Yeah. First, take a shower.
-It wasn't my fault.
-[overlapping chatter]
-Have another towel?
-No way!
-Stop.
Be a good host. Of course we have a towel,
I'll just… I'll grab you one.
You should take the shower first.
Let's let him shower, come on.
-What? Mom!
-Be a good host. Come on.
Go ahead.
[chime plays over speaker]
[Felipe] Eggs, pasta…
Yogurt, light.
Cream cheese, light. It's all light.
This'll be a lot faster.
[lively pop music playing]
DAY 3
SPECIAL PRICE
[music ends]
[student chuckles]
Look, Lardass is buying
the whole store. What's this?
This food isn't all for you, is it?
You gotta be messing with me.
Hold on. The guy needs
a lot of calories to maintain this shape.
[boy] Whoa! Where you goin'? Look.
Don't overdo it with ultra-processed food.
All right, Fatso?
-[mysterious music playing]
-[boys laugh]
I don't care what you say!
I'm fat! So what?
What about that gigantic nose you have?
I bet you could suck up
all the air in the world! And look at you.
You're basically child-sized!
Whoa! Where you goin'?
Look. Just avoid the ultra-processed food.
All right, Fatso?
Ultra-processed food?
I'll ultra-process your face!
[screaming]
[all screaming]
Whoa! Where you goin'? Just avoid
ultra-processed food. All right, Fatso?
-Let me see what we're missing.
-What are you doing?
-Hey, hey!
-[Felipe] Give it back!
You guys still looking
for extra small condoms? Next aisle.
[woman chuckles]
Let's go, Big Jo.
We'll see you around. Loser.
Fucking pricks.
[intriguing music playing]
[music stops]
MORAIS SUPERMARKET
-So, who were those guys?
-No one.
You shouldn't have gotten involved.
My bad.
That shit just gets to me though.
Well, I'm used to it now.
I don't need your help.
[gentle upbeat music playing]
You can put those over there
in the bottom cupboard.
[music fades]
Well? What do you think
of the look? Is it good?
You're going out?
I have a date tonight, with an architect
slash writer slash amateur pilot.
When they hit 50,
every man has an identity crisis.
But tonight we're having Chinese.
Well, have it with Caio.
I don't want to miss the chance
-to get a bit of--
-I don't wanna hear that.
I'm talking about wine.
-[Felipe] Is that all?
-That's all. You heard what I said.
Those weren't on the list.
My week wasn't easy
and these help more than you.
-[Rita] Mm.
-You look great, Rita.
-You should give my mom fashion tips.
-Oh, you're so sweet.
Thank you for that.
Bye, my love.
-Ahh! Have fun, Mom, and lots of wine.
-[Rita giggles]
-You mean actual wine or something else?
-What? Oh, God! You're so gross!
-You don't know how much I love you.
-[Felipe] That's enough. That's enough.
-Ah! Just go. Ditch me.
-[kissing]
My Uber's here, gotta go.
Tell me what Grandma says to you later.
-I love you.
-[Rita] I love you.
Oh, dear.
Uh… Can you put the rest of that
down there for me too, please?
[Caio] Is everything there?
Sure is.
[chuckles] And judging
from the smell, dee… licious.
[gentle whimsical music playing]
Let's eat, then.
[music stops]
[man on TV] Now, with just two hours
to go before Ashley walks down the aisle,
what was once a dream,
may now be turning into a nightmare.
These dress alterations are awful.
This is the most important day of my life.
-Everything has to be perfect!
-[Felipe chuckles]
[man] It's a race against time.
Guests are already arriving for
the most anticipated party of the year.
Gonna call your grandma?
Oh, my grandmother's dead.
Then why'd your mom say to tell her…
What she said, then?
Oh, no, it's just that
ever since she died we like to imagine
that she is using our fortune cookies
to communicate.
Um… "Love your neighbor
like there's no tomorrow."
-Like Good Morning on WhatsApp.
-Yeah.
Yeah.
We like to joke it's her talking to us.
And what did she tell you today?
Let's find out.
[distant dog barking]
[chatter on TV]
"No matter how tall the mountain,
it cannot block out the sun."
She's a little fat-phobic.
[magical music playing on TV]
"An insult says more about the person
who said it than who it was said to."
Sure, tell that
to the person they insulted.
So about… those guys
-at the store.
-At the store? Mm.
I've been bullied, too.
[Felipe scoffs]
What?
That's impossible. Looking the way you do?
You don't know what you're saying, dude.
[Felipe] Hm.
You're back already?
Can you believe he didn't show?
[shoe clatters]
[gentle guitar music playing]
[chuckles]
Looks delicious.
You left me a spring roll. [chuckles]
That sucks, Mom.
Well, at least I had a little wine.
[chuckles]
Mm.
And you…
straight dude,
When you ask a… a girl to go out,
at least do the bare minimum, all right?
The bare minimum, and be there.
Yeah, you got it.
Sorry.
Mm. Mm.
Give your mom a kiss.
Don't stay up too late, okay?
-You two are coming to work tomorrow.
-[Felipe] Love you.
You're gonna love it. Oh, you'll love it.
[kiss]
There's lots to do.
Yeah, you can paint pictures,
and they have classes.
Tomorrow is our dance class.
You can get your body moving up around
and you can get some exercise, Felipe.
Good night.
[door opens]
[music fades]
-May I?
-Mm-hm.
-Well, good night.
-Good night.
["Minto Para Quem Perguntar"
by Anavitória playing]
[lyrics in Portuguese]
["Minto Para Quem Perguntar" fades]
-[lively lounge music playing]
-[Rita] Two, three, step, that's right.
DAY 4
Just like that. And again.
[Rita continues chattering]
That's right. Then return. That's good.
Move those hips around!
Don't watch your feet. Eyes up.
-[woman] Ow!
-I'm so sorry.
Like this. See?
You're such a graceful dancer.
Ah, well, for me, it's just easy.
[Rita] All right, now!
Come here. I want you with Felipe,
he's a good dancer.
Show him the way.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Step back. And then forward.
-[woman] …three, five, six…
-That's it.
Your left leg forward first,
and then the right one.
Four, five, six and six, seven.
And then you repeat the step. See?
[moody music playing]
I'm getting the hang of it.
[Rita] There, that's it!
Good!
One, two, three.
-Dudu, the fatso!
-He's a lardass.
-Hey! Look, guys, he's gonna cry!
-[boy 1] Of course he's gonna cry!
Don't tell me you're gonna cry!
I bet you will.
Why don't you cry to your mommy?
[overlapping chatter]
-What do you think you're doing?
-[kids] Huh? Nothing at all, sir.
-[Felipe] Get out of here!
-[child] Run! Go! Hurry!
[overlapping shouting]
Are you okay?
Don't worry, I'm here now.
Thank you.
That's good. You drew that?
I drew that last week
in Miss Rita's classroom.
I know her well.
She's a really good teacher.
She's crazy, too.
But that's why I like her.
I agree with you.
But don't tell her I said so.
Those idiots are always gonna pick on you.
Best thing you can do, I say,
just stay away from them.
Just go do something happy instead.
You can always draw.
That is the worst advice ever.
Running from a problem doesn't solve it.
He needs real advice right now.
I can tell you that Batman wouldn't run.
And next he'll tell you
that Batman's a billionaire, you know?
Come with me.
I'll give you advice you can use.
Come on, guys.
[rock music playing]
You realize you're just teaching him
how to lose faster?
-Caio, I'm a walking target.
-Relax.
I've got you, okay?
All right guys, come on.
You're mine now. Let's go.
-[man] All right! Let's go.
-[Caio] Come back this way, stay here.
[man] Line up!
-Let's play!
-[blows whistle]
[children shouting]
-Get back, Get back!
-[man] Go!
That guy is killing us!
Go.
You got this! Go, go, go go go!
[rock music ends]
GG!
What'd you just call me?
Uh… GG is "good game."
You say it to each other
when you're online.
Uh, we should go
before child services gets here.
[Caio chuckles]
-I'll have to talk to Marcela.
-I'm going home.
-Goodbye, sweetheart. Love you.
-See you, Mom.
-Okay. Bye, Angela.
-See you later, Rita.
See you later.
Hey, wait!
This is for you guys.
-Well, thank you, Dudu.
-[Caio] It's beautiful.
I'll keep it forever, okay?
See you, Dudu.
-Thank you.
-See you later.
Ah, I see he got my curls, too.
[quiet guitar music playing]
[chuckles]
[bones crack]
[Caio] Oh, poor thing, he's in pain!
[lively action music playing]
That's his problem.
He shouldn't have been so annoying.
You could offer him a comfortable bed,
though. He was so great today.
[Felipe] Oh, so it's okay
for us to hit kids now?
If that's the case,
I should stay with the Joker.
Stop talking!
[pop music playing faintly]
Didn't say anything.
Sorry, I was daydreaming.
[chuckles]
Want to sleep in my room?
-Just because…
-Yes.
…I know sleeping on the couch is awful.
Thank you.
It was really great
what you did for that kid.
Those little idiots had to learn a lesson.
I just know nailing those kids with a ball
was the coolest thing that he's ever done.
[Caio chuckles]
Yeah. It's really hard
not having friends at that age.
[contemplative music playing]
Why'd you disappear, Felipe?
I didn't disappear.
On the contrary, I'd say I've been
getting harder to miss every day.
[chuckles]
I… was really upset that you
suddenly stopped going to the pool.
Then, you grew up and got all… quiet.
And I didn't know
if you were shy, or just a jerk.
But now that I'm here,
it's pretty obvious.
You're definitely a jerk.
[mock gasp]
Oh, I was gonna say
the same thing about you, though, Caio.
[chuckles] But after today, I guess
I would say… You're 50% of a jerk.
[mock gasp]
Weren't there stars on the ceiling before?
Oh, no, they're still there. It's just
that as time goes by they fade, you know?
I remember I tried to get my mom to buy
me some, but she wouldn't let me get any.
They're really hard to take off.
I know. Those stickers
I stuck on my window are still there.
The ones with Mulan?
Ah, don't judge.
I always had a huge crush on her.
It was the only one she allowed.
Of my decorations.
She's still old fashioned
about that stuff.
It's impossible to talk to Caio.
It just doesn't work.
But I thought you said he
spent the whole night talking to you.
Yeah. But this morning…
-Felipe, you heard the new Gaga song?
-[electronic music playing]
Uh-huh.
[in voiceover] Of course I heard it, Caio.
When the greatest artist ever
to walk the face of the Earth
releases new music,
you listen to it the second it comes out.
You don't stop listening
until the next day.
[electronic music continues]
[music stops]
Uh, Lady Gaga is super famous.
Know who she is?
I do know Lady Gaga.
I'm sorry, I just I don't know
what the older generations are into.
Generations? Just how old
do you think that I am?
Uh… How about we get back to the therapy?
Is it possible he knew that your love
for Gaga was a little extreme?
It could be Caio using it
to start a conversation.
That would be so much easier at night.
It would?
But why?
[gentle guitar music playing]
'Cause no one can see you.
All right, here's your homework.
I want you to start a conversation
with Caio during the day.
I'm on vacation, Olivia.
You're assigning homework?
[music stops]
-Hey.
-[man] How's it going, Lipe?
You need anything?
-Nah, I'm just having a quick look.
-Sounds good.
["Idiota" by Jão playing]
Just this.
-That it today?
-Yeah.
-Is this for you or someone else?
-It's a gift.
-How much is it? Ah.
-Only 18.
-Here you go.
-All right, thank you.
He's gonna like it.
[lyrics in Portuguese]
-Hi, Francisco.
-I read that one.
I really liked it. Good stuff.
Ah, it's not for me, it's a present.
Let me know if you ever want
recommendations for fantasy or sci-fi.
Well, thank you.
Have you by any chance seen Caio?
Oh, Caio came down here earlier,
but he went out.
Ok, thanks. See ya.
["Idiota" continues]
-Hey.
-Hi.
DAY 5
["Idiota" stops]
That yours?
Ah, no, I bought it for you.
It's a present.
It's just a little gift,
so don't freak out.
I was going through a second-hand
bookstore and had to get it for you.
-It was on sale.
-No, I'll read it.
Although there's no point,
since I know Gandalf dies in the end now.
[chuckles] I shouldn't
have told you that, I'm sorry.
Going to the movies tomorrow.
You wanna come?
[whimsical music playing]
Um, I would. I already have plans though.
During your vacation?
Yeah.
-That's cool. Well, thanks again.
-[door opens]
I'll go with you.
What about your plans?
Well, I'll talk to my secretary
and have her clear my schedule.
That's cool.
Beca's really going to love you.
[Felipe] Beca?
Of course Caio wouldn't invite me
to go to the movies alone.
What was I thinking?
Obviously, there's a girl.
And what's with that name? Beca?
It sounds like a cheerleader
on some show about high school.
IN LOVE IN HIGH SCHOOL
You're just jealous because
Caio likes me more than you.
Shut your mouth, Beca!
[buzzer rings]
Honestly, you'll love Beca.
She's the best person in the world.
-What will we have to talk about, Caio?
-Relax.
There she is.
[upbeat music playing]
Hi. Just a second.
[Felipe] Guys, this is Beca!
[groans] Thank God you're here.
I couldn't take it anymore. I quit, okay?
[chuckles] Just kidding, Robson.
I'm back tomorrow.
This is Beca.
-Hey there.
-Nice to meet you. Felipe.
The famous Felipe.
He talks about you, you know?
You finally found some time for me, huh?
Felipe, some people,
they disappear off to college,
and start working,
and dating, and forget about you.
-Oh, here comes the sermon. Mm.
-Mm.
-Do you have the tickets?
-[Beca] I do.
Have a good one.
Tell me something.
What's it like having to share a house
with this one? [chuckles]
Ever stub your toe on the corner
of the bed? Or had a root canal?
Or a bad kidney stone?
I like him already.
DAY 6
["To Know the Odds"
by Bárbara Eugênia playing]
[indistinct chatter]
♪ Like drifting memories
That I might live ♪
[indistinct chatter]
♪ What we’re doing now ♪
♪ Apart from being so lost ♪
♪ 'Cause I’d like to know the odds ♪
♪ Like to know the way
It comes down to this ♪
-[loud noise in movie]
-[gasps and screams]
♪ Like the way it was ♪
♪ Like the way
Way we were used to be ♪
That was way better than part two.
The scene where the monster came out
of the screen was better than the sequel.
-Yeah.
-Did you guys like that scene?
Yeah.
Caio doesn't appreciate the beauty
of an exploding head. [chuckles]
What are your favorite scenes from horror?
-Hold on. Uh…
-The Hereditary telephone.
-I loved that one! Yeah.
-Opening scene from Scream, of course.
-And the graduation scene from Carrie!
-Carrie! Oh, yeah!
[Felipe] I am terrified of parties
'cause of that movie.
I'm always waiting for someone
to just pour blood on me.
This would look good on you.
Yeah, well maybe
if there was a bigger size.
["To Know the Odds" continues faintly]
Have you and Caio
known each other a long time?
Ah… He came to my school
in the eighth grade.
We were pretty much
instant friends, you know?
There were no other gays
at our school then. [chuckles]
What do you mean, other gays?
Yeah, other than Caio, I think
there were only three other gays there.
-But Caio's not gay.
-What do you mean, Felipe?
Didn't you know?
There's no way he's gay. Look at him.
No, Caio isn't gay,
because Caio likes football.
And likes to shoot Orcs.
Last week when Cher came up,
I had to explain who Cher was.
-What gay doesn't know who Cher is?
-Who is that?
-Oh, my love, you're beyond help, honey.
-[chuckles]
Caio's not gay, no way. I'd have known.
There's no gay guys who like those things?
Felipe, gay people can be into all sorts
of things that are macho.
They can even be a serial killer.
Mm.
["To Know the Odds" ends]
Um, guys, what's Musical Wednesdays?
Well, it's Wednesday and we're watching
a musical, it's self-explanatory.
And since it's your first time,
you get to choose.
I'll pass. I don't like musicals.
-[gasps]
-[Felipe] I'm shocked.
-My god.
-[Felipe] Dear lord.
-Oh, I don't feel well.
-Try to breathe, Mom.
Caio, in this house,
you can't say stuff like that.
In reality, no one goes around singing.
-No.
-Of course they sing.
They sing so they can
let all of their feelings out.
Not everything has to make sense.
Forget it, you won't understand.
Um, this.
[Rita] Hm.
[video player door closes]
[upbeat guitar music playing]
[music stops]
["Good Morning Baltimore"
by Bel Moreira & Miguel Lallo playing]
[Felipe] Of course he chose this movie.
It's about a fat girl
who's in love with a pretty boy.
I mean, why be subtle, right?
Beca could not have gotten it more wrong.
What kind of gay doesn't like musicals?
Except when the hot guy came on screen…
It was totally obvious.
[dramatic suspenseful music playing]
[music builds to a climax]
[music stops]
Caio is gay!
Well, Now that I think about it,
it's obvious Caio's gay!
All the signs were there.
Lady Gaga. His love for Dodgeball.
His crush on Mulan?
Oh, and those cute little sailor pajamas…
Sorry to bring up the pajamas again,
but I cannot get them out of my head.
[lively funky music playing]
-[exhales]
-[music stops]
[women chattering]
[Felipe] I'm sorry,
but this is more important.
-[woman] But my dog just died.
-[Felipe] Caio's gay! Caio is gay!
-Caio is gay!
-[Olivia] We'll see each other next week.
DAY 7
[Felipe] This changes everything.
I was getting used to the idea
of sharing a room with him, but now…
Are you going to treat him differently
because he's gay?
Well, you make it sound
like I'm homophobic.
If the only problem now
is that you have a crush--
No, stop, stop. First of all, it's weird
hearing you talk like a teenager.
Secondly, I feel nothing for Caio.
Nothing nothing nothing. You know?
No, not at all. Of course not.
If that's true,
how would his orientation change anything?
[whimsical music playing]
Felipe, if Caio didn't tell you before,
he may have had a reason not to.
Of course he had a reason not to.
I already know that.
[thinking] He didn't tell me
that he was gay because I am fat.
I've been stalking Caio.
And in just the past week,
he's already liked 57 photos of boys.
I'll give you a prize if you guess
what they all had in common.
That's right, skinny. They're all skinny.
And that… brings me to him. Denis.
The boy Caio has liked the most
in the past month, my new arch-enemy.
That is, if I had a crush on Caio.
Everyone knows I obviously don't.
All-Soup diet, the ice cube diet,
Ozempic, bariatric surgery…
How am I gonna lose 30 pounds
in two weeks?
I need to make a change.
Not just for Caio, but for my own health.
LOSE WEIGHT QUICK!
RESULTS GUARANTEED
I can't keep being me.
[music stops]
[phone rings]
[doctor] Hm.
[watch beeps]
Mmmm.
Get this… [groans]
You say you wanna lose a few pounds, yes?
-Mm. A lot more than a few.
-I see.
Nowadays, there are
a lot of options for cases like yours.
Can you give me the fastest one?
Oh. The fastest one?
Oh.
[jazzy music playing]
Let's start by cutting all your fat off!
[both screaming]
[music stops]
[panting]
-Ah! Jeez, Caio!
-[dramatic musical stinger]
-Why are you sneaking around?
-I'm just getting water.
Yeah, me too.
But this was in the way though.
I see.
[lounge music playing]
[cereal clattering]
DAY 8
What's with the dark circles
under your eyes?
Hey, Rita, are you sure
I can invite the girls?
[Rita] Of course, why wouldn't I be?
Just that they're a couple.
My mom doesn't like it when--
-Lesbians?
-Oh, the horror!
Lesbians?
[chuckling] Of course,
it's not problem at all.
I almost became a lesbian in college.
-[Felipe] Mom!
-[Rita] What?
One kiss doesn't make you one.
-Who said it was just a kiss?
-Lord, I don't wanna hear all the details.
-Please don't.
-I wanna hear the details.
-Then, I'll tell you later. [chuckles]
-[Caio] Well,
the pool's packed, it's reopened.
So, we'll all be down there
if you wanna come find us.
-Thanks again, Rita.
-Bye for now.
[door opens]
[door shuts]
Don't even try,
you know the answer, all right?
-What? I didn't say anything.
-I can hear you think, though.
[upbeat guitar music playing]
I still won't go, but if I did,
where are my swim shorts?
[giggles] Yes! Oh, I don't believe it!
Mom.
-What is wrong with you?
-[blowing air] Oh, it's just…
[water splashing]
[chuckling]
[music stops]
[Beca] Cannonball!
-You don't know how to do it.
-[gasps]
-Where did you get that?
-Oh, some kid left it here.
I offered to look after it. Name's Harry.
-Potter?
-No… Styles.
Hey, guys, the water's amazing.
Are you getting in?
-In a little while.
-In a while.
[Caio] Mmm.
Aren't you getting in, Melissa?
Usually, "In a little while" is universal
code for not wanting to get in the water.
Yeah, I just prefer to stay on the side.
I don't like being in a bikini
in front of everyone.
Really? Someone as thin and hot as you?
Just because I'm thin doesn't mean
I don't have other insecurities.
Well, that is a crime.
Hey, babe! Get in the pool.
I said, in a little while.
I know. That was a little while ago.
-She's worked out the universal code.
-Mm.
[chuckles]
Come have fun with me,
enjoy the pool and get some sun.
Okay?
[upbeat music playing]
[Melissa and Beca squeal]
[Caio] All right!
[Melissa] Hey!
[girls laugh]
[Caio laughs]
-Third wheel.
-[chuckles]
Remember playing mermaids
when we were kids?
Not really, no.
You really don't want to go in?
-In a little while.
-Hm.
Gays, I was just saying to Mel,
we should go
to the Persimmon Festival tomorrow.
-Let's go!
-Yes. Yes.
-No, I can't.
-[Melissa] You can't?
-I can't go.
-Why?
Ever since what happened at the pool,
I'm not allowed to go out.
She told the doorman, so, no.
-It won't work.
-I think we can figure this out.
How?
It is so hot here,
sweetie, I'm telling you.
And you're not gonna go hang out
with those girls, now, right?
Of course not, mom. I'm going to hang up.
Okay? I love you, goodnight.
All right, good night.
I love you… Oh, he's gone already.
[Felipe] First, we trick your mom.
DAY 9
Then we distract mine with a K-drama.
-[indistinct chatter]
-[lively rock music playing]
Francisco watches games on his phone.
There's always a delay.
-[sports announcer chatters]
-Hey, Francisco.
I think my mom left a key here for me.
No, there isn't one.
-She did.
-She didn't leave anything.
-Goal!
-These are the keys here. Nothing here.
[sports announcer chatters]
Oh, damn delay.
Goal!
What? Where's the goal?
Everyone ready?
Hurry up, let's go, let's book it!
27TH PERSIMMON FESTIVAL
-[person] Whoo!
-[Caio] Wait, guys, Hold on, wait.
Your outfit's a little boring.
I bought it at that store the other day.
I went ahead
and asked your mom what size you are.
-Now we're even. Thanks for the book.
-[Melissa] Put it on.
[Caio chuckles]
-Mm, put it on.
-[Felipe] Can you hold this?
-I got you.
-Come here, come here.
Here.
-There you go.
-[Felipe] Thank you.
[lively festive music playing]
You look good.
[Beca] Now, let's go party!
Let's go. Come on!
[Beca and Caio chuckle]
Let's fix you up.
-By the way, I ship him.
-And who?
-You.
-There is no way that's happening.
-Well, let me believe.
-Okay fine.
[man] Welcome, everyone,
to the Persimmon Festival!
[crowd cheers]
Here are the winners of this year's
contest, Mr. and Miss Persimmon:
Jonathan and Jennifer!
["Me Devora"
by Reddy, Gabeu, Romero Ferro playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[screaming]
I knocked them all down for you.
[all laugh hysterically]
Persimmon! Persimm…!
[Caio] Can I have two tickets, please?
["Meu Pedaço de Pecado"
by João Gomes playing]
[gun blast]
Give me that, you've had too much already.
Go ahead.
-I'm such a good shot.
-How'd you do that?
I'm gonna do another.
-Wow! Yeah!
-I did it!
-[man] Here.
-For me?
-Oh, I am so good.
-[Caio] chuckles]
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
Hey, come here, quick.
Come here, come here, come here.
Hey wait! Where are you going?
-[Caio] Come on.
-Yah!
-Shh! Shh! Shh!
-What's going on?
It's my mom's cousin.
She can't see me here.
Can we wait here a second?
-I always loved these things.
-Oh, wait. Ah.
It's sad you can't go in them
after you're ten.
I know. It's the only kind
of pool I'll still dive in.
Caio, how come
you never told me you were gay?
I don't talk about it.
Only told Beca and Melissa.
Well, you know I'm gay, right?
Yeah, but you're not exactly
trying to hide it. [chuckles]
So then, why are you?
Uh, well, my mom, um…
I think I was like nine or ten.
There was a party for my building.
I was down at the pool.
I was dancing, shaking my hips,
kid stuff, you know?
Of course.
And then, my mom came
and just pulled me away.
[Sandra] Caio Luiz,
stop dancing like that, boy.
You look ridiculous.
Get your stuff, we're going.
She was really upset.
And I didn't understand.
She's been on my case ever since.
Is that why she won't leave
you alone at your house?
Yeah, that too.
Last year my parents went on a trip.
I was staying alone and one day
I forgot my phone at the house.
When I got back to my phone,
there were over a hundred calls.
And my mom thought, I don't know,
that I'd run away. Or got killed.
Or worse, gone out with a boy.
[mock gasp and chuckle]
-[chuckles]
-Have you ever wondered?
About running away?
-What? No. I'm honestly not that brave.
-Are you kidding me?
You dove into this pit
even though you're way too old.
Come on, I'm not that old, all right?
["teu beijo" by Duda Beat playing]
[children giggle]
Let's go find the girls.
Last one there has to marry a priest!
If it's the priest from Fleabag,
I'll go nice and slow.
Thank you, children.
[lyrics in Portuguese]
[whispering] Go, go, go.
["teu beijo" continues]
Shh! Don't wake her up!
Close the door!
-[Caio laughs]
-[gasps]
Caio!
-I can't lay down there now.
-What did you do?
You'll have to sleep in my bed,
and I'll sleep down there.
-No. No.
-What?
Here. Stay here with me.
We'll just sleep together.
["teu beijo" continues]
["teu beijo" ends]
-[distant chattering and shouting]
-[water splashing]
[whistle blows]
[retches and coughs]
[Rita sighs]
You all right?
[toilet flushes]
[Felipe groans]
That wasn't cool, Felipe.
Distracting me with a K-drama.
I really am so happy
that you're making friends.
I really am a super cool mom.
I don't even stop you from going out,
but then you come back plastered?
-I had to tell Caio's mom.
-No.
Yes! I can't hide something
like this from another mom.
Well, then you can return
your cool mom card.
[Felipe groans]
DAY 10
[gentle guitar music playing]
[people laugh and scream]
[water splashes]
HEY STRANGER
WHERE ARE YOU
I'm never gonna drink again.
Oh, that is so cute.
It's your very first time saying that.
-Here. Okay, look at mommy.
-[camera shutter clicks]
You're ridiculous, Mom.
[Rita chuckles]
I'm never eating persimmons again either.
Have you seen Caio?
He left early.
Didn't say where he was going.
What's wrong?
Hm?
Oh, guess I don't know
if we're still cool.
Why? Why wouldn't you still be cool?
Uh, well, that's kind of hard to explain.
Have you considered
actually talking to him about it?
Sometimes it's good to get things out.
I don't need to.
I pay for therapy for that.
Actually, I pay for your therapy.
[Felipe groans]
[gentle guitar music fades]
Felipe? Felipe?
-Felipe, wake up. It's Gandalf.
-Mm.
-It's Gandalf. He's still alive!
-Mmm.
And he's not gray. He's Gandalf the White,
and he's actually way more powerful.
-You disappeared.
-And he knew…
I was texting you all day
and you haven't responded at all.
I'm sorry.
It's just my mom
was getting on my nerves, so…
I went to the park.
I didn't take my phone.
It's fine.
-You okay?
-Yeah.
I thought you were embarrassed
about what almost happened.
What almost happened?
Nothing. Absolutely nothing.
[snickers]
Of course I remember. I'm messing around.
There's someplace cool I wanna show you.
-You trust me?
-[chuckles]
You look exactly like Aladdin.
[both chuckle]
[distant chatter[
[Felipe] I always thought
that this city was so ugly.
[Caio] It depends on how you look at it.
From up here, it's beautiful.
-[Felipe] Caio--
-[Caio] Felipe--
[both chuckle]
You can go first.
I was running away.
Not from you.
The festival was so cool.
And I really felt good.
But I'm feeling something now
I've never felt before.
It's like… I'm finally starting over.
From scratch.
You're like Gandalf.
Yeah.
[Felipe chuckles]
[Caio] Don't you ever wonder
what's beyond those mountains?
[Felipe] Mm, I think it's just
the highway over there.
[Caio, chuckling] Metaphorically speaking.
[Felipe] No, not really.
I just wish I had the courage
to leave the Shire, you know?
Go on adventures,
and do all the things
I didn't do because of others.
Only doing what I want.
Like what?
["Menino Bonito" by Chico Chico playing]
[lyrics in Portuguese]
Go ahead and sit down, man.
DAY 11
It's cool, right?
My mom's gonna lose it.
[chuckles] If your mom's gonna kill you,
imagine what mine'll do.
Ah, well, look who it is.
-Ah. Get a little tattoo?
-Boo!
I wanna see what you got!
Probably got a big one saying,
"High in saturated fat."
-Get off me!
-Tell us, what is it?
-Is it a matching couple's tattoo?
-He actually got your mother's name.
-What was that?
-What did you say, faggot?
Try saying that again, I fucking dare you!
[screams]
-Aaah!
-What's your freakin' problem?
-[all grunting]
-[lively music playing]
Let's go!
[man] Feel the rhythm!
Get up. Come on! Come on!
["i love you" by Billie Eilish playing]
[boy grunts]
[Felipe and Caio chuckle]
♪ It's not true ♪
♪ Tell me I’ve been lied to ♪
♪ Crying isn't like you ♪
♪ Oooh ♪
I've never actually done this with anyone.
Me neither.
♪ Oooh ♪
[Felipe chuckles]
♪ Mmm ♪
♪ Maybe won't you take it back? ♪
♪ Say you were tryna make me laugh ♪
♪ And nothing has to change today ♪
♪ You didn’t mean to say "I love you" ♪
♪ I love you ♪
♪ And I don't want to ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Up all night ♪
♪ On another red-eye ♪
["Good Morning Baltimore"
by Bel Moreira & Miguel Lallo playing]
♪ Oh, oh, oh
Woke up today ♪
♪ Feeling the way I always do ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh
Hungry for something ♪
♪ That I can't eat
Then I hear that beat ♪
♪ The rhythm of town
Starts calling me down ♪
♪ It's like a message from high above ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh
Pulling me out ♪
♪ To the smiles
And the streets that I love ♪
♪ Good morning Baltimore ♪
♪ Every day's like an open door ♪
♪ Every night is a fantasy ♪
♪ Every sound's like a symphony ♪
♪ Good morning Baltimore ♪
♪ And some day when I take to the floor ♪
♪ The world's gonna wake up and see ♪
♪ Baltimore and me ♪
Come on, Felipe, sing!
[in Portuguese] ♪ Oh, oh, oh, I feel
So great Caio's kiss is sensational ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, I don't know
If it's a dream or if it's real ♪
♪ I'm in a musical ♪
♪ I never wanna leave this place ♪
♪ I'm feeling like Miss Persimmon ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, I don't know
If it's a dream or if it's real ♪
♪ I don't want to wake up
It's so good to kiss you ♪
♪ Your warm embrace
Your smile is everything to me ♪
♪ But when I wake up
It all has to come true ♪
-♪ The world will be happier ♪
-♪ Much happier ♪
♪ With you here ♪
-[kissing loudly]
-[crowd cheers]
["Good Morning Baltimore" ends]
[pants]
Caio and I are totally dating now!
-Okay, Felipe.
-No.
First there was an almost kiss
at the Persimmon Festival.
Then he disappeared and I thought
he wanted nothing to do with me at all.
Then he took me to a special place
and he said he was upset with his parents.
And then we just made out.
Then he wanted to get a tattoo.
So I also got one.
Does your mom know this?
-Then I beat up those jerks from school.
-What now?
And then we took one of those
hurricane trolleys back to his place.
At first, we were just
holding on to each other.
Then more.
[gentle guitar music playing]
You're beautiful.
He said I was beautiful.
How did that make you feel?
[chuckles] Good.
It felt great.
And was it as scary
as you imagined it would be, though?
No.
So anyway, basically, we're dating now.
Have you two talked about that?
Olivia, don't you want details?
Jeez, I could never be a psychologist,
Olivia. I would wanna know all the gossip.
And?
I've known him since I was a toddler.
We sleep in the same room.
And we're doing everything together.
If that's not dating, then what is?
It makes me very happy
for me to see you so excited.
It's been quite a while
since I've seen you smile.
But?
But…
You can't just keep living inside
your head, Felipe.
You can't spend your whole life
avoiding difficult conversations.
I really think that you need to talk
to him, and tell him how you feel.
I'm not any good at that though.
Then… write it.
What do you mean?
You spent almost 15 days together, right?
Well, make a list.
Fifteen things that you've learned.
Well that's homework, you know?
Okay, I'll try that.
But I promise,
we're on the same page together.
-[Beca] We're having a party.
-What?
Yeah, a party.
Since my parents are still away.
Not everyone has an apartment that you
can throw a party in. I really like it.
DAY 12
You know that I love parties, right?
I just love them.
No one's gonna throw a bucket
of pig's blood all over you.
You never know what can happen.
And even if they do, it'll get on me.
Because I'm going
to be glued to you all night.
-Beca] Awwww!
-[Melissa] Aww, that is so cute!
-[cell phone rings]
-[Beca] Hold this.
What can I do to help, guys?
I'll be the hype man.
Hey, wait. Guys, be quiet.
It's my mom. Hold on. Hold on, guys!
Hey, ma.
[Sandra] Oh, honey, just look
at this horrible view that I'm stuck with.
Look at this boring view, Caio.
I'm at a restaurant just off…
-Are you at the house, Caio?
-[Caio] Yeah.
I came to get some clean underwear.
[Sandra] Clean underwear? No, Caio,
I packed you a pair for every day.
-Caio, is someone over there?
-[Caio] No, there's nobody here.
Yeah, I just came over here.
[whimsical music playing]
It's all good. I just came over
to get some underwear.
I'm going back to Rita's now.
Oh, well, all right. Fine. I'll just
try calling later. Love you. Ciao.
[music stops]
Oh, God!
Don't say anything.
Mm. Say what?
You were gonna say I look good.
There's no need.
All right, mother, go ahead.
Aww!
You look so cute.
Oh, you're so handsome.
And he'll think the same thing, too.
I'm your mother give me some credit.
You think I don't notice these things?
[chuckles] Mom.
Oh. You look so handsome.
[Felipe] Mmm.
-["Carnaval" by Marina Sena playing]
-[people cheering]
[lyrics in Portuguese]
Hey.
It looks good, doesn't it?
Yeah, it all looks great!
-You look really good.
-[Caio] Thanks.
This wouldn't have happened
if it wasn't for you.
["K.O." by Pabllo Vittar playing]
-Come dance with me.
-Give me a minute, you want a drink?
-Can you get me another?
-Yeah, you bet.
[lyrics in Portuguese]
Hey, what's up?
-Oh, you know.
-Check out how many people showed.
People in this town are bored.
-This is a good song. You coming?
-In a little while.
[groans] I can't believe
Caio invited that guy.
Hello!
Caio has terrible taste
in friends, apart from us.
And you too, of course.
Obviously, you seem great.
-Let's go dance.
-[Melissa] Come with us.
[moody ethereal music playing]
Felipe! Felipe!
-What's wrong?
-Let go.
Where's Felipe?
[alarm blares]
[sirens blare]
-[Beca] I don't understand.
-How did the alarm go off?
Caio kissed another boy.
And Felipe saw.
What? Oh, no.
Felipe, what happened?
I don't want to talk to you, Caio.
Go back to that friend of yours.
Are you talking about Denis?
I didn't wanna kiss him.
Sure, of course you didn't.
It was obvious that you didn't want to.
I thought it was you, okay?
Because we look so similar?
Caio, I'm not an idiot, you know?
When I saw you at the party
you kissed me on the cheek.
I know why it's so hard for me
to come out. Everyone already knows.
They can see it from a mile away.
[Caio] You're the one
who broke up the party.
Think it's easy for me
to kiss another guy in front of everyone?
Then Denis is the lucky one.
Would you just listen for a second?
[car engine starts]
[moody dramatic music playing]
-[police siren blaring]
-No, I won't.
[Rita] Felipe.
[Felipe sobs]
[music becomes quiet]
[music becomes mysterious]
[music fades]
Sweetie?
DAY 13
[distant people chatter and shout]
Caio's parents came back early
because of this whole mess.
He said he was the one
who pulled the fire alarm, did you know?
Caio left already.
Well, it's a shame.
Because he'll miss Musical Wednesday now.
Felipe, Beca already told me
what happened.
-[Felipe shudders]
-I know how you must feel.
No, you don't know!
You have no idea
what I'm feeling right now.
Come on. Everybody gets their heart
broken when they're a teenager.
And you are beautiful,
and incredible, and intelligent,
-and you have to know that--
-Stop, Mom! Stop lying!
-What?
-You don't think I'm beautiful, Mom.
I do. I think you're the most
beautiful thing in the world.
What are you talking about?
Please Mom, just stop.
You don't think I'm beautiful.
If you did, you wouldn't
ever stop me from eating junk.
-You wouldn't worry about my health.
-What are you talking about?
And what do you know about love, Mom?
Even Dad didn't want you.
[moody music playing]
[sniffles]
[Felipe sobs]
[moody music becomes spirited]
[music fades]
[heartfelt music playing]
DAY 14
[music fades]
[door creaks]
[knocking]
[door opens]
[Felipe] Can I come in, Mom?
Of course, sweetheart.
I'm such an idiot.
I'm sorry, I never meant
to say that to you, okay?
I'm really sorry.
Sweetheart, we say the worst things
when we're angry.
Yeah, but that's no excuse, Mom.
[contemplative music playing]
You really like this guy.
Yeah, well, relationships are complicated.
I've been through a lot.
But I really feel like now,
my morale is up.
I'm doing much better.
And even so, I still get upset
when things don't work out.
Well, then that's their loss though.
It sure is.
And I am never going to let…
just a few bad apples
ever make me give up on love anymore.
You sound like one of your K-dramas.
You know what I meant.
I guess what I'm saying…
is never give up on yourself.
You can't throw in the towel
already just because of this heartbreak.
But let me give you
one piece of advice, son…
Never let yourself fall in love
with someone who…
who doesn't make you feel
like you're beautiful.
You too, promise?
Mom,
-I love you.
I do.
Come on, let's see.
"Revenge won't make you feel whole."
"It poisons and kills the soul. "
Wow, your grandma's doing
Chaves impressions now.
-Chaves? Who's Chaves?
-Chaves, from the TV show. Chaves.
-You really haven't heard of him?
-I still don't know.
-What's up?
-Don't look. No, Don't look.
The architect, slash, writer,
slash, pilot is over there.
-He's here?
-Yeah, don't look though, all right?
[intriguing music]
-Sneakers, sports jersey? You kidding me?
-Shh!
I can't believe you actually
cried over a man like that.
[Rita] What are you doing?
Just so you know, you missed out
on an amazing woman, know that?
-Uh, I'm sorry, do I know you?
-How can you treat people like?
-[man] Uh… Listen, I…
-No, no, you have nothing to say! Shh!
Ah, right. Look, it's nothing personal.
I just sort of had a--
Didn't you hear my son?
I have nothing to say to you.
[gentle whimsical music playing]
[both chuckling]
-[Felipe] Ah.
-Thanks.
I don't wanna see you get upset
over someone like that.
You're way too beautiful.
Those bangs are iconic.
[Rita chuckles]
You know what I want?
For me to go and assault the guy?
No!
For you to be exactly who you are,
but kind to yourself.
[gentle upbeat music playing]
I LOVE HAVING FRIENDS
[Sandra] He's not replying to messages,
so he might not have his phone.
-Thank you. What was his friend's name?
-I tried tracking his phone.
Uh, Lígia.
Uh, no, um, I forgot the phone--
-Beca. What about Beca?
-[Sandra] I don't like Beca.
-Sandra, listen--
-God, we had a fight!
We had a fight yesterday,
and when I woke up…
-He had disappeared. He took a whole bag.
-I know.
[Mauro] You have a fight that's one thing,
him disappearing is another.
[Sandra] I don't know. I already…
I… I already tried calling that…
What's going on?
Have you spoken to my son?
Has he called you?
No. No, I haven't talked to him. Why?
Roberto has a friend
at the police department, I'll call.
-Are you sure you haven't heard from him?
-No. No, I haven't.
[Mauro] If there's been an accident,
police can help.
-[Rita] Maybe he's with friends.
-[Mauro] Just protocol.
[Sandra] He doesn't have any.
-[Rita] Where does he go when he's upset?
[dramatic music playing]
[music swelling]
-[music becomes mysterious]
-[panting]
[Caio] I just wish I had the courage
to leave the Shire.
Leave the Shire…
[Caio] Go on adventures.
And do all the things I didn't do…
[ringing]
Hey, I need you over here!
Right Now. Hurry!
DAY 15
[spirited upbeat music playing]
[Beca] This town never has traffic.
[tires screech]
-Beca!
-Shit, I'm sorry.
[car horns honk]
What's going on?
[people shouting]
-Wait, Felipe! Felipe!
-Felipe!
Watch out for cars, Felipe!
[Felipe] Here I am, in a romantic comedy.
Again.
Only this time,
the protagonist in the story is me.
Caio! Caio! Don't get on that bus!
[music fades]
What the hell are you doing?
I can't stay in that house anymore.
I've got an Aunt in Sao Paolo.
I don't know, I'll figure it out.
Someone once told me that running
from problems doesn't solve anything.
Well, this is different.
Caio, I saw your mom.
She's really worried.
Good. That was the plan.
[horn honks]
-I'm sorry, I gotta go.
-Caio, you can't go, all right?
People are staring, Felipe.
So what? I don't care. I don't care!
I don't give a shit if people are staring!
[contemplative music playing]
I've spent my whole life
worrying about what others would say.
I thought that staying hidden in my room
would solve it all somehow.
But you changed that, too, Caio.
Because of you,
I'm not afraid. So thank you.
It's okay if you wanna be
with other guys. I don't care--
-I don't care about other guys.
-[horn honks]
[bus engine revs]
I just… I want you to stay.
I don't care if you're my boyfriend,
I just wanna be with you.
[honks horn]
Look, I've embarrassed myself enough
and don't know what to say, so--
[music becomes uplifting]
-[Beca gasps]
-[Melissa] Ahh!
[bus hisses]
-Maybe you saw a suitcase…
-I don't think so.
A backpack. It was a backpack…
We've established that there was a bag.
The question is where is he going.
-He didn't take a lot--
-There you are!
Caio! Where did you run off to, Caio?
Where in the hell did you go?
How could you do something like that?
Look at your mother!
-She's distraught. How could you run away?
-You weren't at the house!
I'm done running.
I won't run away again.
[contemplative music playing]
What are you…?
You're trying to piss me off, Caio?
Did you know about this, Rita?
That they like each other?
-Yeah, of course.
Of course.
Of course you knew,
and you encouraged it too, didn't you?
-Not at all. We can talk about it.
-I don't wanna talk about it!
-I don't want to talk to anyone at all.
-Okay.
I'm the stupid one.
Mom.
We're dating.
We are?
We are.
I won't run away again,
but only if you can accept me.
I need you to.
We don't recognize you.
-It's like we don't even know you!
-I haven't changed.
I'm just tired of hiding.
This is who I've always been.
All right, look, why don't you… Mauro!
Say something to your son. Tell him. Now!
You aren't gonna say anything?
You have to say something, God!
Are you happy, son?
Well, then it's fine.
No, it's not fine,
it's not fine. No, it's not fine.
No, it's not fine, Mauro.
Mauro, for God's sake, look at me.
You have to talk to your son,
You… He's… He's gonna suffer!
-He's gonna suffer.
-Sandra.
Sandra.
What if…?
[whispering] No, no. No, no.
Just promise me one thing.
Don't ever run away from us again, okay?
[upbeat music playing]
[Felipe chuckles]
What does your grandma say today?
"The whole world is yours."
It's ours.
My therapist gave me
the most boring assignment ever.
Here are 15 things I learned
in the last 15 days.
Oh, this could be a while.
Oh? May I?
Go ahead.
"I really like when we talk.
And I like watching TV with you."
"I like going out on errands
and dancing."
"I even like playing dodgeball."
-[chuckles]
-[kids cheer]
"Turns out I really,
really like having friends."
"I like spending the whole day
with them, Doing nothing."
"I learned that I don't look bad
in plaid or red."
"And getting drunk on persimmon
liqueur is possible."
[chuckles]
"I learned that I can be strong
when I need to be."
"But it's okay to ask for a hug
when things are tough."
That's all?
I love those sailor pajamas
with the little shorts.
[both chuckle]
I also like hearing you talk
about the things that you like.
I like kissing you
and touching you.
And you, you are
everything I want and more.
[sniffles]
Thank you.
[Felipe sniffles]
By my count,
there's still one thing missing.
Do you trust me?
[upbeat music continues]
[both chuckle]
[exhales deeply]
[both scream]
["Flutua" by Johnny Hooker playing]
[lyrics in Portuguese]
[Beca and Melissa squeal]
[Beca and Melissa laugh]
["Flutua" continues]
["Flutua" fades]